<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<siteinfo>
    <site>
        <name>RailYatri</name>
        <desc>With over 23.9 million passengers traveling and commuting daily by train, RailYatri aims to serve its passengers with inclusive and comprehensive information that helps those making informed decisions, thus simplifying their train is a premier portal for Indian Railways train travellers. We strive to be the fastest, mobile-friendly site that answers all your train travel questions in a few taps. A comprehensive hub of train travel information that dedicatedly works to give its users insightful information, all under one roof, to help them plan and take their train travel decisions in a better way.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Amazon</name>
        <desc>The Tech giant is the largest Internet retailer in the world as measured by revenue and market capitalization, and second largest after Alibaba Group in terms of total sales. The Amazon.com website started as an online bookstore and later diversified to sell video downloads/streaming, MP3 downloads/streaming,audiobook downloads/streaming, software,video games,electronics,apparel,furniture,food,toys and jwellery. The company also owns a publishing arm,Amazon Publishing,a film and television studio,Amazon Studios produces consumer electronics lines including Kindle e-readers,Fire tablets,Fire TV and Echo devices.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Myntra</name>
        <desc>Now a part of Flipkart, Myntra is one of the topmost fashion e-retailers in India, with a huge range of latest fashion apparels and fashion accessories for men, women and kids, and home and lifestyle products.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Bigbasket</name>
        <desc>Big Basket is Indias leading online grocery store delivering almost everything from fruits, vegetables to meat, packaged foods, toothpastes, liquid soaps and other home and kitchen essentials. If you have a blog or site that talks about food, cooking, or running a household then the Big Basket affiliate program is for you. Its uncomplicated, advantageous and free.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Jabong</name>
        <desc>Jabong offers fashion or sports apparels, shoes, bags, belts, or other fashion accessories for men, women and kids. Jabong.com is an Indian fashion and lifestyle e-commerce portal founded by Praveen Sinha, Lakshmi Potluri, Arun Chandra Mohan and Manu Kumar Jain. The portal sells apparel, footwear, fashion accessories, beauty products, fragrances, home accessories and other fashion and lifestyle products. The company's headquarter is in Gurugram, NCR, India. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Snapdeal</name>
        <desc>Snapdeal is an Indian e-commerce company based in New Delhi, India. The company was started by Kunal Bahl and Rohit Bansal in February 2010. As of 2014, Snapdeal had 300,000 sellers, over 30 million products across 800+ diverse categories from over 125,000 regional, national, and international brands and retailers and a reach of 6,000 towns and cities across the country. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Lenskart</name>
        <desc>Lenskart is Indias leading online shopping portal for eyewear. With a country-wide reach including cities such as Delhi, Mumbai, Kolkata, Chennai, Bangalore and Ahmedabad, online shopping India has been made easy with Lenskart. You can order from a gamut of options ranging from eyeglasses to contact lenses to sunglasses for men and women. It provides a platform for people to spice up their life with the latest international runway trends at amazing prices. Lenskart is Indias online shopping portal that gives great discounts and amazing offers on a daily basis. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Paytm</name>
        <desc>From being a mobile recharge solution to a full-fledged e-commerce store and now the frontrunner of Cashless India mission, Paytm has come a long way in a very short time. With Paytm, you can recharge phones, DTH cards; pay bills: landline, mobile, gas, water et al, book flights, trains, cabs, hotels; pay insurance premiums, school fees and more. Apart from that, Paytm also offers its customers a wide range of products across categories like fashion, electronics, home décor, automobile accessories, musical instruments etc. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Paytm mall</name>
        <desc>Paytm is India's largest mobile payments and commerce platform. It started with online mobile recharge and bill payments and has an online marketplace today. In a short span of time we have scaled to over 200 Million registered users.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Shopclues</name>
        <desc>One of the top five marketplaces in India, Shopclues brings you everything: from clothes to automobile accessories, from home and kitchen products to electronics, from baby care products to sports and fitness products and more.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Amazon app  install</name>
        <desc> TheTech giant is the largest Internet retailer in the world as measured by revenue and market capitalization, and second largest after Alibaba Group in terms of total sales. The Amazon.com website started as an online bookstore and later diversified to sell video downloads/streaming, MP3 downloads/streaming,audiobook downloads/streaming, software,video games,electronics,apparel,furniture,food,toys and jwellery. The company also owns a publishing arm,Amazon Publishing,a film and television studio,Amazon Studios produces consumer electronics lines including Kindle e-readers,Fire tablets,Fire TV and Echo devices.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Lybrate app install</name>
        <desc>Lybrate is the best way to seek medical help. To make it seamless and smooth, we beat onerous challenges every day to ensure easy access to doctors for billion people, creating an experience that is truly magical for both healthcare experts and users. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Abhibus</name>
        <desc>Abhibus is an online marketplace for cheapest bus tickets and hotel rooms in India. Our android app helps users to book bus travel and hotels in a quick, simple and secure way. Our app allows users to book bus tickets from across 100000 bus routes offered from over 2,500 bus operators and access to over 125000 rooms across India.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Snapdeal app install</name>
        <desc> Snapdeal is an Indian e-commerce company based in New Delhi, India. The company was started by Kunal Bahl and Rohit Bansal in February 2010. As of 2014, Snapdeal had 300,000 sellers, over 30 million products across 800+ diverse categories from over 125,000 regional, national, and international brands and retailers and a reach of 6,000 towns and cities across the country. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Stalkbuylove app install</name>
        <desc>StalkBuyLove, an online retail company founded by Europe based experts in the fashion industry, provides chic and trendy apparel suited to the tastes of every fashion forward lady at addictive prices. At StalkBuyLove.com, we are inspired by global trends to create apparel and accessories that women not only admire but relate to as well. As varied as fashion is, each woman's choice is not just limited to the ongoing fashion trends and new styles, but also includes how she feels that day. Keeping this in mind, each collection houses different designs, style and prints to meet your every mood, whim and fancy. That's why it is the perfect destination for online shopping for girls when it comes to clothes shopping. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Taskbucks app install</name>
        <desc> At TaskBucks, we are making 'time spent on smartphones' more rewarding. You try new apps or engaging with existing ones, share your feedback with app developers and for all this you earn Bucks.Use TaskBucks for :- Free mobile recharge and Data recharges</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Tata Cliq app install</name>
        <desc> Tata CLiQ is a first-of-its-kind Physical marketplace that combines online shopping with the offline store experience, to serve over one million customers.
            Within a year from launch, Tata CLiQ is in the Top 10, and one of the fastest growing, e-commerce websites in the country.Engage with us online in a seamless shopping experience across desktop, tablet and smartphone. Explore the best Indian and international brands across clothes and accessories (watches, bags, shoes and more), gadgets and appliances. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Testbook app install</name>
        <desc> Testbook decided to walk the last mile in achieving digital accessibility in every remote corner of the country. Partnering with local classrooms, Testbook empowered teachers to build online test centres in every street of the country. Testbook is No.1 website for Online Exam Preparation. Practice Free Mock Tests with Best Quality Questions Based on Latest Pattern and Syllabus.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Goibibo</name>
        <desc>Goibibo is Indias leading online travel booking brand providing range of choice for hotels, flights, trains, bus and cars for travelers. Our core value differentiator is the most trusted user experience, be it in terms of quickest search and booking, fastest payments, settlement or refund processes. Through GoStays, our customers enjoy standardized stay experience at certified hotel properties.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Foodpanda</name>
        <desc>Since 2013, millions of users have ordered food online with us, helping us grow and to become better to the point of offering food online from thousands of restaurants across India. We still uphold the same motto making online food ordering fast and easy. Our service allows you to find all of the restaurants available nearby, which can deliver to your house. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Swiggy</name>
        <desc>Swiggy is one of Indias fastest food delivery services. With its no minimum order policy, live order tracking and super-fast delivery; it has really made ordering food amazingly smooth and swift </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Makemytrip(flights)</name>
        <desc> Indias pioneering online travel company, MakeMyTrip offers instant booking and comprehensive choices to travelers, while the MakeMyTrip affiliate program offers a great money-making opportunity to online publishers. Whether you are a travel blogger or run a travel website, you get the chance to earn some great MakeMyTrip affiliate commission on sale of domestic and international flight tickets via your site. Since the travel website and app offers a smooth booking experience, great discounts, and a super-efficient customer service, the MakeMyTrip affiliate program becomes one of the easiest and best ways to multiply your earnings.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Dominos</name>
        <desc>One of Indias best pizza restaurants, Dominos has been delivering lip-smacking pizzas, and a host of other side orders like breads, pastas, dips, desserts, beverages and more. They also offer excellent quality, first-class service, affordable prices and guaranteed timely delivery. Thus, it is little wonder that online orders for pizzas have increased by over 170% lately.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Cleartrip</name>
        <desc> We come together each day to fulfill a promise of offering the single most comprehensive travel experience to users, through award winning Mobile and Desktop solutions. With intuitive products that have the largest selection of flights, hotels and trains, we keep customers at the centre of everything we do.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Bigrock</name>
        <desc>Bigrock is a highly well-known name in the domain registration and web hosting market, offering an assortment of specialized web services. Website builder tool, web hosting, digital certificate, reseller hosting and VPS hosting are some of the highest Big Rock affiliate marketing payout categories available currently.. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>McDonalds</name>
        <desc>One of the most popular American fast food chains in the world, McDonalds serves around 68 million customers daily in approximately 36,899 outlets spread across 120 countries. Present in India since 1996, McDonalds has over 400 outlets in this country serving its delicious burgers, French fries, puffs, wraps, desserts, coffees etc. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Urban Ladder</name>
        <desc>Urban Ladder is a design-led, omnichannel brand which offers end-to-end solutions for furniture and home decor. With over 5000 designs across 35 categories such as living, dining, bedroom, study, and decor. Urban Ladder was established as an online-first brand in 2012.Urban Ladder has distinguished itself as a design-led brand that has established a prominent place in the urban Indian home. Its furniture and decor products are closely curated and designed by its in-house design and sourcing teams.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Internshala</name>
        <desc> Connecting 25,00,000+ students with 80,000+ companies in India, Internshala is the most trusted platform for student internships in India; the one-stop place for students to gain work experience, earn exciting stipends and begin their career.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>1mg</name>
        <desc>1mg.com brings to you an online medicine store, which can be accessed for all health needs. With 1mg.com, you dont just buy medicine online, but can also book appointment with the best doctors nearby. We are focused towards making healthcare accessible and affordable, and so give you plenty of options in terms of medicine substitutes. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Acko</name>
        <desc> Acko is to insurance what the internet is to information and what the instant message is to communication. We figured that most people dont really care for insurance, simply because they dont understand it. But you dont really need to. Thats what we are here for.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Adidas</name>
        <desc>The brands of adidas complement each other in a unique way to help athletes perform better, play better, feel better. Our products break records, set trends, make history. Every day. All over the world. Welcome to the adidas Group. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Agoda</name>
        <desc>Agoda is one of the worlds fastest-growing online hotel platforms. Established in 2005 as a start-up, Agoda expanded quickly in Asia and was soon acquired in 2007 by the worlds largest seller of rooms online  the Priceline Group. Today, Agoda offers hundreds of thousands of accommodation options around the globe with service and support in over 40 languages.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Airtel</name>
        <desc>Bharti Airtel Limited is a leading global telecommunications company with operations in 20 countries across Asia and Africa. Headquartered in New Delhi, India, the company ranks amongst the top 4 mobile service providers globally in terms of subscribers. In India, the company's product offerings include 2G, 3G and 4G wireless services, mobile commerce, fixed line services, high-speed DSL broadband, IPTV, DTH, enterprise services including national and international long distance services to carriers.</desc>
    </site>

    
    <site>
        <name>Nykaa</name>
        <desc>Nykaa is an e-commerce website offering beauty and wellness products from all the leading brands such as Lakmé, Kaya Skin Clinic, L'Oréal Paris and many more.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Aakash</name>
        <desc> Aakash Institute is one of the well known institutions in the country that provides comprehensive test preparatory services to students for preparation of medical entrance examinations. The Institute initially commenced operations in Delhi with a few students but with a vision of Mr J.C. Chaudhry, a prominent teacher and an educationist. Some of these students cracked the medical entrance exam securing top ranks making Aakash one of the sought after coaching institutes for preparation of medical entrance exams.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Akbar Travels</name>
        <desc> Akbar travel is India's largest travel company providing best solutions to ease travel for customers, not only India but International as well. Flight booking became easier with Akbartravels Travel portal. In addition to strengthening its existing services to customers and travel partners, much new travel- related products are added to the website. Akbar travels success extended when low-cost airlines serving to Gulf countries associated directly with them like Air India, Air Arabia, and Fly Dubai. It's a one-stop shop for passengers to buy tickets in out India with best prices.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>AliExpress</name>
        <desc>AliExpress is a global retail marketplace offering quality products at factory prices in small quantity. AliExpress is an online retail service based in China that is owned by Alibaba.Launched in 2010, it is made up of small businesses in China and elsewhere, such as Singapore, that offer products to international online buyers. It is the most visited e-commerce website in Russia and was the 10th most popular website in Brazil.It facilitates small businesses to sell to customers all over the world, and one can find almost anything for sale. It is more accurately compared to eBay, as sellers are independent, using AliExpress as a host to sell to consumers and other businesses.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Beardo</name>
        <desc>Beardo was born out of the lack of options for the discerning urban male, who likes to grow and maintain his beard, but has no alternative other than using ordinary oils or incompatible products. At Beardo we use the choicest ingredients and quality controlled manufacturing processes to give the bearded man, the products he needs to ensure that his face mane, is pampered, soft, shiny and smells impeccable.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Beato</name>
        <desc>BeatO app is a smart Diabetes Care and Management App that connects Glucometer to your smartphone, facilitating proactive monitoring and analysis by Diabetes Health Experts. Get expert guidance also. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Bata</name>
        <desc>Bata India is the largest retailer and leading manufacturer of footwear in India and is a part of the Bata Shoe Organization.Incorporated as Bata Shoe Company Private Limited in 1931, the company was set up initially as a small operation in Konnagar (near Calcutta) in 1932. In January 1934, the foundation stone for the first building of Bata.s operation - now called the Bata. In the years that followed, the overall site was doubled in area. This township is popularly known as Batanagar. It was also the first manufacturing facility in the Indian shoe industry to receive the ISO: 9001 certification. </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Biba</name>
        <desc>BIBA has always been known for fashionable ethnic wear for women at affordable prices. Kurtas and kurtis are an important part of every Indian womans wardrobe. You are sure to be spoiled for choices when you see BIBAs diverse range of Salwar Kurtas, Churidar Kurtas, Anarkali Suits, Kurta with Lehenga, and striking dupattas in myriad colors.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Cashify</name>
        <desc>At Cashify, our mission is to transform the way people sell their old gadgets online. We help you unlock the highest price for your old gadget with the least amount of effort. Through our localized network of professional buyers across the country, we make sure you are able to sell your old or used gadgets in the fastest way possible and get the best customer experience.</desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Bluestone</name>
        <desc>Established in 2011, BlueStone is India's No.1 online jewellery destination that showcases high quality fine jewellery with strikingly exquisite designs.We aim at revolutionizing real jewellery and lifestyle scenario in India with a firm focus on craftsmanship, quality and user experience. In a short span of time BlueStone has built a large family of loyal consumers in India and abroad. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Bookmyshow</name>
        <desc> BookMyShow offers show times, movie tickets, reviews, trailers, concert tickets and events near you . Also features promotional offers, coupons and mobile app.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Booking.com</name>
        <desc>Established in 1996 in Amsterdam, Booking.com has grown from a small Dutch start-up to one of the largest travel e-commerce companies in the world. Part of The Priceline Group (NASDAQ: PCLN), Booking.com now employs more than 15,000 employees in 198 offices in 70 countries worldwide. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Cipla Immuno Boosters</name>
        <desc>Cipla ActivKids Immuno Boosters is a tasty nutritional supplement, designed to build immunity in kids aged 2 years and above. It is available in a tasty choco-bite format.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>EasymyTrip</name>
        <desc>EaseMyTrip from home-garage in May 2008. Within 3 months they lost all investment (incurring losses due to fraud conducted by some miscreants). To heck with it, they thought, and decided to give it another try. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Expedia India</name>
        <desc>Expedia is one of the fastest growing online travel portals in Asia, offering travellers an extensive selection of hotels, activities and travel services to meet every budget and activities of every kind at competitive rates. With over hundreds of thousands of hotel partners worldwide and a comprehensive offering of flight inventory made available on the website, travellers can book everything they need for a holiday - rooms to meet every budget, activities of every kind and travel services to complement. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Faasos</name>
        <desc>Faasos is an Indian "food on demand" company that was incorporated in 2011. Faasos operates in the 16 of the largest cities in India and takes customer orders via its mobile app and also the website. It is the only vertically integrated food business in India and operates all three stages of a "food on demand" business: ordering, distribution and order fulfillment.Faasos receives 10,000 orders a day across India and has recorded a growth rate of 20-25 per cent month-on-month.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>FirstCry</name>
        <desc>A Mahindra venture, Firstcry is one of the most popular portals in India for baby care products.While looking after a child is time-consuming and exhausting, so is shopping for him/ her.Firstcry helps all time-crunched parents by bringing a wide range of baby care products like toys, books, diapers, nursing necessities, clothes etc. from thousands of national and international brands at their doorstep. Also, the baby care industry in India is expected to grow at an annual rate of over 17% in revenue during the 2014-2019 period. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Hotels.com </name>
        <desc>Hotels.com is a leading provider of hotel accommodation worldwide, offering booking services through its own network of localised websites and telephone call centres.Hotels.com gives travellers one of the widest selections of accommodation on the net, including both independent and major chain hotels as well as self-catering in over hundreds of thousands properties worldwide. The company offers a one-stop shopping source for hotel pricing, amenities and availability and also specialises in providing travellers with accommodation during sold-out periods. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Himalayan</name>
        <desc>Himalaya's story began way back in 1930. A curious young man riding through the forests of Burma saw restless elephants being fed the root of a plant, Rauwolfia serpentina, which helped pacify them. Fascinated by the plant's effect on elephants, this young man, Mr. M. Manal, the founder of Himalaya, wanted to scientifically test the herb's properties.
            With no money and only a pocketful of dreams, he pawned his mother's jewelry to buy a hand-operated tableting machine. The years that followed were a time of endurance and a test of the young man's patience, strength and passion. He spent his days learning about herbs from neighborhood healers and his nights working on the machine to make a few hundred tablets. His vision was to 'bring the traditional Indian science of Ayurveda to society in a contemporary form'. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Hostgator</name>
        <desc>HostGator is a global provider of web hosting and related services.Founded in a dorm room at Florida Atlantic University by Brent Oxley, HostGator has grown into a leading provider of Shared, Reseller, VPS, and Dedicated web hosting. HostGator is headquartered in Houston and Austin, Texas, with several international offices throughout the globe. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>JetAirways</name>
        <desc>Jet Airways, India's premier international airline which provides you with one of the finest experiences across the skies. Our high standards of service and reliability, efficient operations and focus on innovation has enabled us become one of India's favorite domestic and international airline.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Koovs</name>
        <desc> When it comes to trendy fashion online, Koovs is a go-to place for all kinds of apparels, footwear, fashion accessories, jewellery and beauty products for both men and women. Here you will find everything from Indian brands to international high street brands, along with some great discounts from time to time.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Lenovo</name>
        <desc>Lenovo is a $US30 billion personal technology company  and one of the top two PC makers globally, serving customers in more than 160 countries. Dedicated to building exceptionally engineered PCs and mobile internet devices, Lenovos business is built on product innovation, a highly efficient global supply chain and strong strategic execution. Formed by Lenovo Groups acquisition of the IBM Personal Computing Division, the Company develops, manufactures and markets reliable, high-quality, secure and easy-to-use technology products and services.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Limeroad</name>
        <desc>Limeroad.com is the best online shopping site for all you fashionable women and men who never let style slip away. We have a collection featuring the latest apparels, accessories, footwear as well as home décor for all you fashionable people to shop from. What you find on Limeroad is right whats trending. We keep our catalogue updated with the latest trends so you never go out of style. Make Limeroad.com your ultimate shopping site and stay trendy always. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Med Life</name>
        <desc>MEDLIFE's mission is to help families achieve greater freedom from the constraints of poverty, empowering them to live healthier lives.Buy authentic medicines online with discounts from Medlife. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>MyBusTicket</name>
        <desc>MyBusTickets.in is the top online bus booking site for India, built by engineers to make online bus booking easy and convenient. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Netmeds</name>
        <desc> Netmeds.com, India Ki Pharmacy, is brought to you by the Dadha and Company  one of Indias most trusted pharmacies, with over 100 years experience in dispensing quality medicines. At netmeds.com, we help you look after your own health effortlessly as well as take care of loved ones wherever they may reside in India. You can buy and send medicines from any corner of the country - with just a few clicks of the mouse.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>PizzaHut</name>
        <desc>It was the summer of 1958 when Dan and Frank Carney decided to open a pizzeria. With mouth-watering pizzas prepared by the founders themselves, Pizza Hut soon became the most popular neighbourhood restaurant. From then to over 13,200 restaurants across the world today, we have come a long way. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Samsung  e-store</name>
        <desc> Its an ever-changing world and Samsung wants to put you in the middle of it all. Were dedicated to creating innovative technologies, processes and products that expand the horizon of whats possible and enrich people's lives.</desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Shein</name>
        <desc>SHEIN prides itself on offering on-trend styles catering to both young women and teens, that wont break the bank. SHEIN is able to stay on top of the latest fashion trends from around the globe while rapidly bringing these styles to market. So whether youre searching for boho dresses and graphic tees or patterned blouses and chic swimwear, SHEIN is the ultimate one-stop-shop for the modern yet economical fashionista. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Titan eyeplus</name>
        <desc>Titan Eyeplus, the third major line of consumer business division from Titan Company Limited, ventured into the eyewear category in March 2007. The move was an initiative to redefine the industry and straddle the marketplace with exacting quality standards, unparalleled in Indias prescription eyewear industry. Benchmarked against the best in the world, Titan Eyeplus heralds standardization in the eyewear industry. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>TravelGuru</name>
        <desc>Travelguru is India's leading travel website, offering you the best prices on flights, hotels and holiday packages across India and the world. Travelguru makes planning and buying a holiday or a business trip easy and convenient.Travelguru's current product offering consists of airline tickets, hotel rooms, vacation packages and cruises. We will shortly be expanding our services to offer a wide array of travel-related services including car rentals. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Dell</name>
        <desc>Dell empowers countries, communities, customers and people everywhere to use technology to realize their dreams. Customers trust us to deliver technology solutions that help them do and achieve more, whether theyre at home, work, school or anywhere in their world. Learn more about our story, purpose and people behind our customer-centric approach. </desc>
    </site>
    
    <site>
        <name>Airtel</name>
        <desc>Bharti Airtel Limited (commonly shortened to Airtel and stylised airtel) is an Indian global telecommunications services company based in New Delhi, India. It operates in 20 countries across South Asia and Africa. Airtel provides GSM, 3G, 4G LTE mobile services, fixed line broadband and voice services depending upon the country of operation. Airtel had also rolled out its VoLTE technology across all Indian telecom circles except Jammu and Kashmir and is likely to launch in this circle soon.It is the second largest mobile network operator in India and the third largest mobile network operator in the world with over 438.04 million subscribers </desc>
    </site>

    <site>
        <name>Amazon prime</name>
        <desc>Amazon Video is an Internet video on demand service that is developed, owned, and operated by Amazon. It offers television shows and films for rent or purchase and Prime Video, a selection of Amazon Studios original content and licensed acquisitions included in the Amazon's Prime subscription. </desc>
    </site>
    
</siteinfo>


